https://swiss-financial.ch/privacy-policy/

Home
About UsCareersContact UsLocationsOur ServicesFamily OfficesFund InvestorsInvestment Managers
Search
Home
About UsCareersContact UsLocationsOur ServicesFamily OfficesFund InvestorsInvestment Managers
Privacy Policy
This overall privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire Swiss Financial Services Group ("SFS") website. At SFS, we respect your privacy and have taken strong steps to protect your privacy online as outlined in this document.Information Disclosure
Except as described in this privacy policy, where clients have opted in to certain disclosure, we do not disclose information about your individual visits to SFS, or personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, personal profile, etc., to any outside parties, except when we believe it is required by law or to protect SFS, our users or others.
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our web server, analyzing data, providing administrative assistance, and providing other services. These other companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any third party.
SFS may from time to time aggregate certain information about the demographics or use of the website. Such information is in aggregate form and not at the individual level.
Links and References to Third Parties
The SFS website contains informative links to other third-party sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those web sites. We do, however, encourage our partners to adopt privacy policies similar to this one.
Updating the Privacy Statement
If we decide to update our privacy statement at SFS, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website please contact us at:
Swiss Financial Services AG
Hallenstrasse 10
8008 Zurich
Switzerland
Telephone:+ 41 44 267 7400Facsimile: + 41 44 267 7422Email: services@swiss-financial.ch
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
